Guide to the Chloe Faith Dzubilo Papers 1976-2011 MSS.397
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series I: Artwork, 2004-2010; 275628
  - Untitled (Private Room), 2008; 275855 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Untitled (The Spirit Prevails Tragedy), 2008; 275856 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Untitled (Spuritual Drag), 2009; 275857 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Untitled (The Stable Closed), 2008; 275858 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Untitled (Stay in the Loop), 2008; 275859 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Untitled (Stranger Than Life Itself), 2008; 275860 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Untitled (Surrender), 2008; 275861 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Untitled (T-Girls), 2008; 275862 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - [Untitled], undated; 275863 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - [Untitled], undated; 275864 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Photographs, 1983-2004; 275629
  - Chloe and Lollipop Calendar by Katrina Del Mar, 1998; 275865 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Framed Photo of Chloe, undated; 275774 (Box 6)
  - Photos by Alice O'Malley, 2010; 275866 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Photos by Katrina Del Mar, 2008; undated; 275867 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Photos by Richard Phibbs for Paste Magazine, undated; 275868 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Photo of Rosario Dawson with Writing, undated; 275869 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Photo by Tanyeth Berkeley, 2007; 275870 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Photo by Tanyeth Berkeley, 2007; 275646 (Folder 15 Right)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Writing, 1988-2010; 275630
  - Envelope - Annotated, undated; 275871 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Kodak Box - Annotated, undated; 275872 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - [Untitled Writing], undated; 275873 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Who Killed Brandon Teena The Second Time?? Posters - Annotated, 1994; 275874 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- OVERSIZE Series V: Press & Ephemera, 1984-2011; 275631
  - Press, 1997-2004; 275875 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Transisters Poster, undated; 275876 (Box 4, Folder 42)